Guide to the Stanford University Objects Collection SC1048
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Objects
  - Squeezable stress-reduction toy in the shape of a Marguerite bus, ARCH-AM-2007-010 (Box 1)
  - Stamps, Accession ARCH-AM-2018-011 (Box 1)
    Framed Sheet of Breast Cancer stamps, Presented to Stanford University from the US Postal Service
  - Stanford African Students Association t-shirt and trophy, ARCH-AM-2010-004 (Box 1)
    2010-004.1 SASA t-shirt, dark grey 2009 2010-004.2 trophy from 2008 SASA World Cup
  - Stanford Association Centennial Medallion, 1991; ARCH-AM-1993-02 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Axe Committee t-shirts (4), 1987-1993; ARCH-AM-2002-24 (Box 1)
    2002-24.1 1987 red, patch with tree over S; polo style 2002-24.2 1989/90 red, patch with axe over S; polo style 2002-24.3 1991-92 red, patch with tree over S over axe; polo style 2002-24.4 1993-94 burgundy, patch with tree over S over axe; polo style
  - Stanford band hat (1956-1962), ARCH-AM-1980-01 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner. Red felt, with "Stanford" in white, Indians across lettering; white felt border. 25 x 43 cm, circa 1960; ARCH-AM-1981-01 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner on bamboo cane, ARCH-AM-00-169 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Banner on Flag Pole. Pole 3x273 cm long. Stanford seal on Blue Bkg., ARCH-AM-00-262 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, red cloth with "Stanford" in white cloth letters, 3x6'., circa 1907; ARCH-AM-1980-05 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, red felt with white felt letters, 3 x 6 ft. It hung in Dink Templeton's Encina Room, 1920, 1921; given to donor in 1921., ARCH-AM-1977-03 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, red felt with white felt square, red "S", ARCH-AM-1977-08 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, red felt, "Stanford" in white felt, swallow tail, on black bamboo pole. 38x80cm, crooked pole, 90cm., ARCH-AM-1984-29 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, white letters on red felt; block letters, double pointed ends. 16 x 31 in., ARCH-AM-1979-10 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, white letters on red felt; gothic lettering. 14 x 34 in., ARCH-AM-1979-09 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner, white letters on red, 34 x 29 cm., ARCH-AM-1984-50 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner: white letters on square red felt backing, ARCH-AM-1981-08 (Box 1)
  - Stanford banner. red felt bkg. with Stanford in white letters. Indian at one end. 74x29cm., ARCH-AM-1980-17 (Box 1)
  - Stanford belt buckle (brass?), ARCH-AM-1995-21 (Box 1)
  - Stanford-Binet Intelligence Scale Form L-M Test Kit, 1960; ARCH-AM-2013-001; 1 item(s) (Box 1)
    Briefcase containing test manuals written by Lewis M. Terman and Maud A. Merrill, various puzzles and tests for children, instructions for administering the test, and scoring procedures.
  - Stanford Block "S" sweater awarded to Dorothy Cone, class of 1928, awarded for women's shot put, circa 1928; ARCH-AM-2007-031 (Box 1)
  - Stanford buttons (three), 1978-79; ARCH-AM-1980-12 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Centennial items, ARCH-AM-1991-103 (Box 1)
    1991-103.1 paper visor "Stanford 100 Years" 1991-103.2 paper napkins Stanford University Centennial Commencement 1991 (2) 1991-103.3 sew-on patch: Planting for the Second 100 Years Stanford 100 1991-103.4 Button: 100 years of staff diversity 1991-103.5 small trowel, unmarked
  - Stanford Class Shield. 53X31 cm, wooden shield, Block "S" in brass., 1911; ARCH-AM-00-185 (Box 1)
  - Stanford decals and memorabilia of L. Timothy Portwood, circa 1975-2008; ARCH-AM-2009-040 (Box 1)
    AM 2009-040.1 football bumper sticker: This is your brain [Stanford helmet] This is your brain on drugs [Cal helmet] AM 2009-040.2 decal: Stanford Fooball more than a passing fancy AM 2009-040.3 pennant from Portwood's retirement party 2008 AM 2009-040.4 plastic cup: 2000 World Series Champions New York Yankees AM 2009-040.5 Pin from Yankee Stadium World Series September 9, 2001 AM 2009-040.6 ticket stub Yankee Stadium World Series September 9, 2001 AM 2009-040.7 Cap (blue and yellow: L & M Shop & Cap factory, SF) date unknown
  - Stanford diploma and teaspoon, ARCH-AM-1994-10 (Box 1)
    1. 1892 Diploma of V.C. Richards (framed) 2. teaspoon of Memorial Church in Bowl
  - Stanford family portrait in 12 x 16 inch frame (purple velvet with stones), ARCH-AM-00-058 (Box 1)
  - Stanford flag (red cloth, no lettering) attached to wooden rod, rolled and inserted in wooden case 14" long, ARCH-AM-1982-09 (Box 1)
  - Stanford high power pulsed Klystron with plate that reads: "Dr. Edward Ginzton, our director, co-worker, and friend. From the members of the W. W. Hansen Laboratories of Physics.; 1949-1959", ARCH-AM-1996-02 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Hillel T-shirts, ARCH-AM-1996-04 (Box 1)
    1) Red & White, Stanford (?) in Hebrew 2) "Killer Maccabees" ) Blue - "Stanford Hillel"
  - Stanford Indian decals: 13 items (4 designs), ARCH-AM-1993-05 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Indian doll; cloth, with red felt "sweater" with "S"; single red feather. 27 cm tall, ARCH-AM-1981-02 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Indian memorabilia, ARCH-AM-2011-004 (Box 1)
    AM 2011-004.1 Stanford Indian lighter; AM 2011-004.2 Stanford Indian belt buckles (2); AM 2011-004.3 Stanford buttons: “I’m a Big Red Rooter” (2); “Get Tough Big Purple”; AM 2011-004.4 Stanford buttons: “Stanford Indians”; “Once an Indian Always an Indian” (2); AM 2011-004.5 Ceramic Indian with Stanford ‘S’; AM 2011-004.6 Ceramic Indian on canoe; AM 2011-004.7 Stuffed Stanford Indian doll; AM 2011-004.8 Stanford Indian penant; AM 2011-004.9 Indian drumming doll; AM 2011-004.10 Indian/bird ashtray
  - Stanford jacket belonging to William A. Stone, class of 1961, circa 1960; ARCH-AM-2010-003 (Box 1)
  - Stanford jacket: red wool with leather sleeves and "Stanford" emblem on left side, ARCH-AM-2002-31 (Box 1)
  - Stanford jewelry, 1922; ARCH-AM-1977-01 (Box 1)
    1. watch fob, "S", class of '22 2. SU tie pin (1922) 3. El Tigre Club lapel pin (1922)
  - Stanford Leather belt and buckle, 1924; ARCH-AM-1979-04 (Box 1)
  - Stanford memorabilia, 1985; ARCH-AM-2005-041 (Box 1)
    2005-041.1 T-shirt of Manzanita court [MANZANITA Stanford's Adult Luxury Mobile Home Community]; 2005-041.2 handwritten sign ""you can break the bonds of apartheid"" with red cloth strings attached
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-1996-12 (Box 1)
    Pillow cover Bookends (3 sets) Belt & buckle Placard with Stanford seal Stanford seal with pin
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-00-042 (Box 1)
    042.1 Red felt banner with STANFORD in white; PEG '23 written on lower right corner 042.2 Granite paperweight keepsake from Pace program "For Service to Stanford 1961-1964" 042.3 Granite paperweight keepsake from Pace program "For Service to Stanford 1961-1964"
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-2004-008 (Box 1)
    008.1 framed printed illustration of Memorial Church, pre-06 008.2 tip tray, ceramic, made in Germany, with image of Mem Church (no steeple) 008.3 Stanford belt buckle with seal (very worn) 008.4 glass bottle from University Pharmacy, F. J. Steinmetz, Palo Alto, ca. 1905 008.5 ceramic tray (small) with east arch of S.U., made in Germany for Oscar Promis, San Jose
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-2005-024 (Box 1)
    024.1 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.2 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.3 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.4 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.5 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.6 Stanford Laundry bag, red logo on white 024.7 Playing cards with U. seal, 2 packs in box 024.8 Playing cards with U. seal, 2 packs in box 024.9 Pour spout for liquor bottle with carved Indian head wearing red beanie with "S"
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-2006-006 (Box 1)
    006.1 wooden box (5.75 x 3.75 in.) with CUE at Stanford burned into top 006.2 Stanford Think Again cube (unfolds into assorted images) 006.3 Paperweight: The President's Fund Stanford University 1993-1994 Founding Member (brass seal of U. imbedded in plastic or clear resin?) 006.4 Four assorted Centennial pins 006.5 Label pin with tree on it 006.6 Pin of mortar board (black enamel) inscribed on back ""B.J.D. 1948""
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-2016-010 (Box 1)
    2016-010.1 Stanford #1 button (red with white letters) 2016-010.2 Stanford #1 button (red with white letters) 2016-010.3 Stanford button (red with white stripe and red letters) 2016-010.4 Axe the Bears button (lenticular with Indian and bear) 2016-010.5 Ceramic stein (white and red with seal on one side, block S on other side) 2016-010.6 Ceramic ash tray, white with gold seal 2016-010.7 Necktie, red background with "Stanford" printed repeatedly in white (diagonally) 2016-010.8 Red silk tie with Indian painted in white on front 2016-010.9 Red Rose Bowl felt pennant with image of stadium, roses, Indian printed in color, and "Stanford" printed in white 2016-010.10 Red felt pennant with image of Indian printed in color, and "Stanford" printed in white
  - Stanford memorabilia - athletic and alumni, ARCH-AM-1993-01 (Box 1)
    Two tumblers: Coach of the Year - 1951 - Chuck Taylor Four tumblers: Class of 1927's 50th Reunion (1977) Indian Joe doll, with drum (battery operated) Plaque on stone: "for service to Stanford 1961-64" Stanford PACE program Glass pitcher engraved with AEO [Alpha Epsilon Theta]
  - Stanford memorabilia - athletic and alumni, Accession ARCH-AM-2017-004
    - Memorabilia (Box 1)
      AM-2017-004.001: Tote bag, "Cap and Gown Women Leaders at Stanford"; AM-2017-004.002: Sweatshirt, red with white embroidering: "Stanford University"; AM-2017-004.003: Letter jacket, red with cream leather sleeves; AM-2017-004.004: Golf shirt, red and white stripes, with Block S; AM-2017-004.005: Neck tie, black, with Block S and Tree embroidery; AM-2017-004.006: Pennant: Red with White lettering.
    - Memorabilia (Box 2)
      AM-2017-004.007, AM-2017-004.008: Mug, white "Class of '46 30th Reunion" with L'il Injun holding a mortarboard and helmet; AM-2017-004.009, AM-2017-004.010: Coasters, Buck/Cardinal Club, white with "Support Student Athletes: Invest in Future Leaders"; AM-2017-004.011 Beanie, red/white reversible; AM-2017-004.012: Bucket hat, white with Block S, Tree, Stanford embroidery, green inside brim; AM-2017-004.013: Visor, white with "Stanford" in red lettering; AM-2017-004.014: Baseball cap, red with "Stanford" embroidered in white with black outline; AM-2017-004.015: Baseball cap, red with white trim and Stanford Indian patch; AM-2017-004.016: Pipe cleaner, red, in Block S shape; AM-2017-004.017: Keychain, white Stanford helmet; AM-2017-004.018: Belt buckle, Stanford in silver lettering with red background and silver border; AM-2017-004.019: Money clip, Injun Invitational, red with Indian head, 1969; AM-2017-004.020: Money clip, gold, "84th NCAA Golf Championships, Stanford" with Block S, 1981; AM-2017-004.021-AM-2017-004.022: Rings, silver with Axe and Block S; AM-2017-004.023: Pin, white football with S; AM-2017-004.024: Pin, silver Block S with red background; AM-2017-004.025: Pin, red "Stanford Football" with gold Block S; AM-2017-004.026: Pin, "Old Pavillion 1922-1989" with basketball; AM-2017-004.027: Pin, "Old Pavillion 1922-1989" with basketball; AM-2017-004.028: Pin, "Hundredth Big Game, 1997"; AM-2017-004.029: Pin, "Stanford Football: Serious Football, Serious Fun, 1998"; AM-2017-004.030: Pin, "46: Stanford 55th Reunion"; AM-2017-004.031: Button, "Stanford Class of '46" with helmet and mortarboard; AM-2017-004.032: Pin, "Once an Indian, Always an Indian, Class of 194[6]" (6 taped over another year); AM-2017-004.033: Button, red "I'm a Big Red Rooter!"; AM-2017-004.034: Button: "Stanford Half Century Club: '42 '92"
  - Stanford memorabilia: 6 pennants (3 with seal, 3 with Indian head), 1 banner, tennis bag, Indian doll and stuffed horse, cap printed with the 1984 football schedule, ARCH-AM-2006-004 (Box 1)
    2006-004.1-.3 Pennants with U. seal 2006-004.4-.6 Pennants with Indian head 2006-004.7 Banner: "Stanford" with U. seal 2006-004.8 Cap with football schedule 2006-004.9 Bag, red & white striped canvas with "Stanford Tennis" 2006-004.10 Indian doll, wearing shirt with red "S" 2006-004.11 Stuffed horse (red) with white "S" on each hip (brand reads "A College Pet") 2006-004.12 Button: Class 1944 Once an Indian Always an Indian (with Lil Injun face)
  - Stanford memorabilia: beanie and megaphone, ca. 1931; football pins, ca. 1963, ARCH-AM-2002-25 (Box 1)
    2002-25.1 freshman beanie, red felt 2002-25.2 Roos Brothers megaphone [poss. originally blue and gold] 2002-25.3 football pin "Stanford Indian" with football charm 2002-25.4 football pin "Stanford Indian" with helmet charm 2002-25.5 football pin "Stanford Indian" with helmet charm (flat)
  - Stanford memorabilia, ARCH-AM-2017-023 (Box 1)
    Programs, buttons, pennants, belt
    2017-023.01 - Red felt pennant with Indian and Stanford in white; 2017-023.02 & 2017-023.03 - Medals (2) - Stanford 57 Continuing Connection 50th Reunion. Gold & red medal with red ribbon; 2017-023.04 - Button, "Stanford Football," white background with black lettering and Block S in red; 2017-023.05 - Button, white background with Block S in red; 2017-023.06 - Button, Tostitos Fiesta Bowl, January 2, 2012, black background with football/Block S in foreground; 2017-023.07 - Button; "Coming up Roses Stanford 01-01-00," square with red background; 2017-023.08 - Pin, "57 Stanford 45th Reunion," silver, white, black, red; 2017-023.09 - Pin, "57 Stanford 50th Reunion," silver, white, black, red; 2017-023.10 - Lanyard, red with Stanford and Block S in white; 2017-023.11 - Belt buckle and belt, Stanford in brass on buckle, brown leather belt; 2017-023.12 - Luggage tag, metal with "1916" and Stanford seal; 2017-023.13 - Luggage tag, brass with "1911" and Block S in red; 2017-023.14 - Luggage tag, brass "18" inside Block S; 2017-023.15 - Luggage tag, brass "18" with seal; 2017-023.16 - Patch, red with Stanford in white; 2017-023.17 - Felt Block S, white; 2017-023.18 - Block S, white/red; 2017-023.19 - Red felt pennant on dowel with Stanford in white.
  - Stanford memorabilia, Accession ARCH-AM-2017-024 (Box 1)
    Stained glass, red Block S with white background; Scarf, red and white with “Stanford” in red; Cap, white with “Stanford” embroidered in red, with 18 Stanford pins; Necktie, cardinal red with “Stanford” pattern in white; Cap, red mesh with “Stanford Cardinal” and Block S on front; Cap, red mesh with “Stanford University” and “Block S” on front; Buttons, Stanford (50, various); Pins, Stanford (43, various); Decals, Stanford (17, various)
  - Stanford mugs and shot glass, miscellaneous, ARCH-AM-2010-008 (Box 1)
    2010-008.1 Stanford Humanitites Center mug; design copyright 2001 by davey hubay 2010-008.2 Clear plastic mug with "STANFORD" in red letters and 3 pennant shapes below 2010-008.3 Shot glass "Branner Hall 1991-1992" with image of a penquin
  - Stanford of Today printing die, unknown; ARCH-AM-2010-001 (Box 1)
    Metal printing die, badly damaged.
  - Stanford pennant, with Lil Injun caricature, red felt, with white painted design., circa 1960; ARCH-AM-1980-03 (Box 1)
  - Stanford pennants; athletic sweaters, 1919-1921; ARCH-AM-1979-13 (Box 1)
  - Stanford pins owned by Jennie Hughes Hutchison, class of 1910, ARCH-AM-1995-08 (Box 1)
    1. Phi Beta Kappa pin 2. Pin of S.U. seal with "10" also on it 3. Stanford Pennant pin
  - Stanford seals, ARCH-AM-1981-06 (Box 1)
  - Stanford student hat (George A. Tarbell), 1906; ARCH-AM-1988-02 (Box 1)
    Red wool hat, somewhat like a Fez, with tassle; '06 written on it. G. Tarbell '06 written on inside brim.
  - Stanford sweatshirt: Red, hooded (child's size), in white on front "Stanford" with Lil Injun symbol., circa 1960; ARCH-AM-1980-02 (Box 1)
  - Stanford sweatshirt, red with slightly modified U. seal on front, circa 1968; ARCH-AM-2009-020 (Box 1)
  - Stanford sweatshirt: red, with "Stanford" and Lil Injun in white., Accession ARCH-2017-026 (Box 1)
  - Stanford the Game (board game), ARCH-AM-1985-05 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Think Again cube, unfolds into different images, 2001; ARCH-AM-2009-025 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Tree costume worn by Judy Mischel, 1980-82; ARCH-AM-1984-04 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University 119th Opening Convocation fan (program), 2009; ARCH-AM-2009-039 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University book cover: seal on front, S INDIANS on spine, and L'il Injun on back; plasticized paper, ARCH-AM-2005-005 (Box 1)
  - Stanford University embossing and foil stamping dies, unknown; ARCH-AM-2009-031 (Box 1)
    2009-031.1 University seal, 1/2 inch 2009-031.2 University seal, Â¾ inch 2009-031.3 University seal, 7/8 inch 2009-031.4 University seal, 1 and 1/8 inch 2009-031.5 University seal, 1 inch 2009-031.6 University seal, 1 Â½ inch 2009-031.7 University seal, 1 inch 2009-031.8 University seal, 1 Â¾ inch 2009-031.9 Seal with lone tree, 1 1/2 inch 2009-031.10 University seal, 1 1/2 inch 2009-031.11 Letter,, 3 inch tall 2009-031.12 Shield for Medical School, 1 1/2 inch 2009-031.13 Hoover Institution, 2 1/2 inch 2009-031.14 Lane Medical Library (image of Hopkins with Hopkins Medical Library; arched over portrait) 3 1/2 inches tall 2009-031.15 University seal with lone tree, 3 inches 2009-031.16 University seal with lone tree, 5/8 inch (2 items) 2009-031.17 Herbert Hoover Medal for Distinguished Service 2009-031.18 University seal, 5/8 inch (2 items) 2009-031.19 University seal, 5/8 inch 2009-031.20 University seal, 1 3/16 inch 2009-031.21 University seal, 1 3/8 inch 2009-031.22 University seal, 1/2 inch 2009-031.23 University seal with lone tree, 1 3/4 inch 2009-031.24 Shield for Medical School, 7/8 inch 2009-031.25 Shield for Medical School, 1 3/16 inch 2009-031.26 Plate with four 1-inch University seals
  - Stanford University leather postcards, ARCH-AM-2010-009 (Box 1)
    2010-009.1 to Miss Irene Withers; features Stanford coed and RAH-RAH-RAH STANFORD, with other notes 2010-009.2 to Miss Jennie Withers; features large red S, with notes 2010-009.3 to Miss Jennie Withers; features candle, book, pennant, with notes 2010-009.4 to Miss Jennie Withers; features coed holding pennant and RAH-RAH-RAH STANFORD, with other notes
  - Stanford University seal (metal) on wooden plaque originally owned by Henry Dorrance Owen, Class of 1912, circa 1910; ARCH-AM-2010-014 (Box 1)
    Metal University seal (8.25 in. diameter) with Die Luft... on wooden shield (14 in. high)
  - Stanford watch fob, 1924; ARCH-AM-1979-05 (Box 1)
  - Stanfordopoly game, 2nd edition, 1989; ARCH-AM-2001-11 (Box 1)
  - Stereoptican, made by Underwood & Underwood., ARCH-AM-00-255 (Box 1)
  - Stereopticon viewer, ARCH-AM-2000-038 (Box 1)
  - Sticker on Grand Opening of Stanford Bookstore, 1991-05; ARCH-AM-1995-04 (Box 1)
  - Sticker; 11x11 cm. red, yellow, black. Palo Alto Shell Gasoline; with Mem Chu and Stanford S., ARCH-AM-00-203 (Box 1)
  - Sticker, Stanford axe, ARCH-AM.2014-013 (Box 1)
  - Stickers, various, 2016; Accession ARCH-AM-2017-007 (Box 1)
    A new CS with "Nerd Nation" glasses/Stanford Cardinal Service; KZSU 90.1 FM Stanford "The New Zoo" http://kzsu.stanford.edu with zebra and radio tower; "Of Course I'm a Feminist/Stanford Women's Community Center wcc.stanford.edu"; ARTS/arts.stanford.edu/students, @stanfordarts (3 stickers, each in different color).
  - Stickers, Stanford Libraries Nerd Squirrel (7-Various), circa 2017; Accession ARCH-AM-2018-004 (Box 1)
  - Sticky Wilson Candy Boxes, ARCH-AM-2008-021 (Box 1)
    2008-021.1 Wooden, Figure of Co-Ed and Pennant on Front 2008-021.2 Wooden, Figure of Co-Ed in White Skirt and Red Hat
  - Sticky Wilsons chocolates box, candy store (Palo Alto/Stanford) for 1/2 lb., ARCH-AM-1983-09 (Box 1)
  - Stone 13x16cm with bevelled end and significance unknown., ARCH-AM-00-209 (Box 1)
  - Stone carving from Quad renovations, probably discarded by stone carver. 20x8x7cm., 1984; ARCH-AM-1984-24 (Box 1)
  - Stonecutters' tools, used in construction of LSJU; 9 items with tag, ARCH-AM-00-039 (Box 1)
  - student athletic memorabilia - arrived with regular accession 92-042, ARCH-AM-1998-015 (Box 1)
    98-015.1 belt buckle "STANFORD" (1929)- 2.75 in. 98-015.2 fencing medal won in 1933 98-015.3 fencing letter (senior manager): red S inside red circle on white felt - 7.5 in. square
  - Student hats and painting of an '07 student. Photos of the great-grandchildren of Myron C. Burr wearing these hats boxed with item 036.1, ARCH-AM-00-036 (Box 1)
    036.1 Plug Ugly 1907 (Myron C. Burr) 036.2 Plug Ugly 1911 036.3 Plug Ugly 1906 036.4 Sophomore Dink of Myron C. Burr '07 036.5 Sophomore Dink 036.6 Beaver top hat [fairly damaged] 036.7 Senior Sombrero of Myron C. Burr 036.8 Watercolor painting by Edie D. Kellogg of an '07 male student
  - Student memorabilia owned by Carl Zahner, ARCH-AM-2009-014 (Box 1)
    2009-014.1 Stanford beanie 2009-014.2 Stanford pennant (red felt) 2009-014.3 Black felt square appiqued with red "S" and a football in one corner 2009-014.4 Button (white "S" on red) with red & white streamers and metal football
  - Student registration cards, framed. From Pioneer Class: 1891-1895, ARCH-AM-00-174 (Box 1)
  - Students' standard cell, manufactured by the Eppley Laboratory, Inc., stamped May 28, 1930 on information card tacked to the backing. CAUTION: contains mercury [but is safe to handle], ARCH-AM-2005-006 (Box 1)
  - Stuffed cow available during Christmas season, with bell and "S" and note re origin of "the Farm", ARCH-AM-1997-003 (Box 1)
  - Stuffed cow, black & white with bell. With tag re origins of "The Farm.", 2001; ARCH-AM-2002-23 (Box 1)
  - stuffed toy - character with glasses, pencil behind ear, red cap with "", and sweater with S2K. 6 3/4 inches tall, ARCH-AM-1999-022 (Box 1)
  - stuffed tree (evergreen variety), with red lips, ARCH-AM-1999-021 (Box 1)
  - Styrofoam "straw" hat with red paper band "Stanford": from 1971 Rose Bowl, ARCH-AM-1994-05 (Box 1)
  - Styrofoam forms for construction of balusters [RETURNED IN 2006], ARCH-AM-2004-028 (Box 1)
  - Suitcase, straw. 66X38X17 cm. Contains honorary Degree Hoods awarded to Ray Lyman Wilbur, with list., ARCH-AM-00-188 (Box 1)
  - Superbowl memorabilia, ARCH-AM-1984-21 (Box 1)
    1. Banner- superbowl, Jan. 20, 1985; white with red, blue aqua printing 2. Cap- superbowl, white with red blue printing. Super Bowl 3. Pin- badge (Superbowl Sunday). Green with black lettering.
  - Super Bowl XIX Shirts, 1985; ARCH-AM.2015-010; 4 item(s) (Box 1)
    ARCH-AM.2015-010.1 White T-shirt with blue collar and sleeves, front: blue & red stripes, 4 football players "Super Bowl XIX; Stanford University January 20, 1985"
    ARCH-AM.2015-010.2 Grey cropped T-shirt, front:"Super Bowl XIX; Stanford Stadium Stanford, California January 20, 1985"
    ARCH-AM.2015-010.3 White T-shirt with red ring collar and red ring sleeves, front: SF 49ers helmet logo "1984 NFC Champions San Francisco 49ers, Super Bowl XIX; Stanford Stadium Stanford, California January 20, 1985"
    ARCH-AM.2015-010.4 White Sweatshirt with red stripes, front: "Super Bowl XIX; Stanford Stadium Stanford, California January 20, 1985"
  - Sunglasses, 2012-2013; ARCH-AM-2014-017; 2 item(s) (Box 1)
    ARCH-AM.2014-017.1 "Stanford 2012" ARCH-AM.2014-017.2 "The Stanford Fund/Stanford 2012"
  - Sweater; grey sweatshirt by Mayo Spruce sports wear; on front: portrait of Prof. J. T. Watkins, with name underneath. Produced by Student Art Association after Watkins won popular vote of students [see clippings]., 1962; ARCH-AM-1981-10 (Box 1)
  - Sweater, Athletic. 76X53 cm. Knit laces at neck. Long collar, green and blue horizontal stripes, and long sleeves., ARCH-AM-00-133 (Box 1)
  - Sweater, Athletic. Jersey, sleevless, white, diagonal red strip with "S" on stripe. 35X81 cm., ARCH-AM-00-138 (Box 1)
  - Sweater, Athletic. White, sleevless, with yellow "W". 36X76 cm. Jersey., ARCH-AM-00-137 (Box 1)
  - Sweater, Block S. Red, pullover, v-neck., ARCH-AM-2017-020 (Box 1)